http://www.profeximages.com/privacy-policy/

Log In
Create Account
My Cart CheckoutRedeem Print Credit
Professional Photography & Digital Services905-428-2712
PROFEX IMAGESProfessional Photography & Digital Services905 - 428 - 2712
HomeWEDDINGPORTRAIT
Family PortraitHeadshotsEngagementDating Profile PhotosMaternityBabyFirst Year Baby PlanMORE SERVICES
Commercial PhotographyEventsschools & clubsDecor Photo FramesFloatmount Photo DisplayPortfolioDIGITAL SERVICES
Photo RestorationPhoto Borders & Edge EffectsPhoto CollagesAlbums + Photo booksPhoto Birth AnnouncementsPhoto Thank You CardsSave the Date CardsPhoto Christmas CardsPhoto SlideshowsSlideshow SamplesWorkshopsClients
MENU
MENU
Home BlogWEDDING PORTRAIT PORTRAIT
Family Portrait
Headshots
Engagement
Dating Profile Photos
Maternity
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY:Any personal information collected on this website via contact forms, order
forms, etc... will not be shared, sold or leased to any third party. This information is used strictly by Profex Images to process orders and to notify users of special promotions and news.
Any email addresses collected on this website are never shared, sold or leased
to any third party.Profeximages.com collects some non user specific information such as the type of browser and operating system used. This information is used to assist us internally to provide the best site design and format for our users. The information is not shared with anyone outside of profeximages.com. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please send an email to privacy@profeximages.comAt any time, should you no longer wish to be contacted by us, send us an email to privacy@profeximages.com with the word “REMOVE” in the subject line.
Sign up to get notifications of our latest Specials and new products
Your information is safe with us and won't be shared.
You can unsubscribe at any time.
no thanks
Thank you for signing up!
Close
Serving Durham Region (Ajax, Pickering, Whitby, Oshawa, Bowmanville, Port Perry) and Toronto (GTA) in Ontario since 1987 905-428-2712
CONTACT US    ~    FAQ     ~
PRIVACY POLICY    ~    WEDDING RESOURCES
©2020 All Rights Reserved.
Content may not be used without prior express written consent.
